易考范文二十七
What we can see is a thought-provoking scene.
At an exhibition of letters to and from family members,
it occurs to a college student that he hasn't written to his parents
since he was enrolled in college three years ago.
The scene confronts us with this question:
what can we do with handwritten letters,
a communication tool used to be important to people but now about to disappear?
In recent years,
handwritten letters gradually give way to other means of communication
such as telephone, cell phone and email,
mainly because the modern tools are faster and more convenient.
Just by pressing several keys,
people can talk to others or send messages to them in no time.
However, it takes people days, even weeks, to receive a letter.
But on the other hand, handwritten letters have advantages
over these technological products.
First, letters written by the sender himself can express more feelings
in his heart of hearts than the impersonal typed words.
As what people used to write in their letters,
seeing the words, see the person.
That is to say, when we are reading a letter,
it seems as if we had a face-to-face talk with the sender.
Moreover, letters are for us to taste and treasure.
Even a century later,
our later generations can read them and share our pain and joy.
My dear friend,
pick up a pen and write on a sheet of paper a few lines
to the one you care about. Because the time spent on writing a letter pays.